Guide to Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref174
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- (No. 16) The Ruins of Cesarea (a woman carrying a child at the beach at the beach at Qisarya/Cesarea (duplicate Ref8, 38))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000058; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Coast; Water; Beaches; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Women; Children; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Caesarea/Qisarya
- (No. 74) The Chapel of the slaughter of the Infants (two views of the Chapel of the Milk Grotto (duplicate Ref33))., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000059; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Paintings; Lanterns/Lamps; Bethlehem; Chapel of the Milk Grotto of Our Lady
- A group of people near a body of water, with boats on the horizon., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000060; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Beaches; Water; Seas; Men; Children; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Coast; Palestine
- A group of people near a body of water, with boats on the horizon., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000061; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Paintings; Men; Women; Architecture; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Religious Imagery; Mountains/Hills; Buildings; Jerusalem
- Two views showing the entrance to Christ's Tomb in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre (duplicate Ref50)., Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000062; Narinsky, Sonia; Narinsky, Shlomo; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
  Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums; Postcards; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Religious Sites; Churches; Lanterns/Lamps; Religious Crosses; Jerusalem
- An empty page in the "Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album.", Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000063; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)
- The back cover of the "Shlomo Narinsky (Neroni) and Sonia Narinsky Postcard Album.", Circa 1910-1921; AD_MC_030_ref174_000064; Narinsky, Shlomo; Narinsky, Sonia; 1 Photographic Prints (E-records Electronic Records AD_MC_030_ref174)